Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
- Box: 101, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 101, Folder 45)
  - Item 8: Underutilization of Women Workers, 1967; Publication (Box 101, Folder 45)
    Notes: August 1967
  - Item 9: College Women Seven Years After Graduation Resurvey of Women Graduates - Class of 1957, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 45)
    Author: Jean A. Wells and Muriel B. Wool
    Notes: Bulletin 292 1966
  - Item 10: Report of Michigan Conference on Problems of Employed Women, 1961; Publication (Box 101, Folder 45)
    Notes: Sept. 30, 1961 Held at Kellogg Center, Michigan State University East Lansing, Michigan
  - Item 11: facts about Women's Absenteeism and Labor Turnover, 1969; Publication (Box 101, Folder 45)
    Author: Jean A, Wells
    Notes: August 1969
- Box: 101, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 101, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Report of University of Iowa Conference on Employment Problems of Working Women, 1963; Publication (Box 101, Folder 46)
    Author: Edited by: John J. Flagler, Mario F. Bognanno and Craig Lloyd
    Notes: Held at Iowa Memorial Union Iowa City, Iowa May 10-11, 1963
  - Item 2: Child Care Arrangements of Working Mothres in the United States, 1968; Publication (Box 101, Folder 46)
    Author: Seth Low and Peral G. Spindler
    Notes: Children's Bureau publication number 461-1968
  - Item 3: Careers for Women in the 70's, 1973; Publication (Box 101, Folder 46)
  - Item 4: Careers for Women as Technicians, 1962; Publication (Box 101, Folder 46)
    Notes: Women's Bureau Bulletin 282
  - Item 5: Equal Employment Opportunities for Women Under Title VII of the Cvil Rights Act of 1964, 1965; Publication (Box 101, Folder 46)
    Notes: October 1, 1965
  - Item 6: everybody's talking about Trained Workers for the Future, 1963; Publication (Box 101, Folder 46)
    Notes: Revised July 1963
  - Item 7: How Can you Help Reduce Barriers to the Employment of Mature Women, 1969; Publication (Box 101, Folder 46)
  - Item 8: Automation and Women Workers, 1970; Publication (Box 101, Folder 46)
    Author: Jean A. Wells
    Notes: February 1970